Thank you for waiting.
お待たせ
It's been a while.
久しぶりです
The atmosphere has changed quite a bit.
雰囲気まただいぶ変わったね
Is it true?
本当ですか?
It feels so spring-like.
めっちゃ春っぽい
surely.
確かに
Isn't it cold?
寒くない?
today.
今日
I'm surprisingly dressed up.
意外と着込んでるんだ
TRUE?
本当?
I see.
そうか
I feel like I can go to work normally.
このまま普通に出勤しそうな感じ
surely.
確かに
cute.
かわいい
Okay, let's go then.
よし、じゃあ行こうか
It's not like I'm in a hotel today, so
今日いきなりちょっとホテルじゃないから、
On the other hand, it has a very date feel to it.
逆にめっちゃデート感あっていいな
surely.
確 かに
I think this is actually more fun.
むしろこっちの方が楽しみだと思う
Seriously, the clothes you wear every time are cute.
本当、毎回着てる服かわいいよね
It's been a while since I came here.
すけい久々に来たな
Do you usually go?
普段行く?
Friends and stuff.
友達とかと
I go sometimes.
たまに行く
Let's go.
行くんだ
Yeah, sometimes.
うん、たまに
I think young people these days don't go to karaoke.
イメージ的に最近の若い子ってカラオケ行かない感じかなと思う
But.
けど
Maybe I'll go there once in a while.
た まに行くかな
Let's go.
行くんだ
Yeah.
うん
Eh, I see.
えー、そっか
Well, I'm good at something.
え、なんか得意なの
Honeyson or something.
ハニソンとか
Yeah, but I think it's a pretty famous song.
えー、でも結構有名な曲だと思う
Is that so?
そうなの?
Eh, I'm singing something.
えー、なんか歌ってるの
Rather.
むしろ
I want to see you sing.
歌ってるところが見たい
oh yeah.
そうそう
Like me, that stuck with my uncle.
僕 みたいなね、おじさんにはそれの刺さりした
Will you sing Marigold?
マリーゴールド歌うか
That's fine.
いいじゃん
Yeah.
うん
That's kind of how I feel about recent songs,
なんかもう、感覚的にそれ、最近の曲の感覚なんだけど、
That was quite a while ago.
結構前だよね
It came out quite a while ago.
結構、出たのは結構前だよね
That's right.
そうだよね
6 years ago.
6年前
Six years ago, I was still in high school.
6年前って、まだ高校生とか
High school students.
高校生とか
Eh.
えー
That's terrible.
やばいな
It's insanely good.
むちゃくちゃうまいね
Well, really.
えー、ほんと
Um, while singing,
あの、なんか、歌いながらこっち、
Sometimes I see things like this.
たまにこうなんか見てくれるんだ
That's so cute.
あれ、めっちゃ可愛い
Super cute.
超可愛い
Eh, what?
えー、なに?
What?
何が?
Eh, what is it?
えー、なんだろう?
But it's kind of like that.
でも、なんかあれだね
The way I feel now, I feel like I can sing anything.
今の感じだと、なんでも歌えそうだね
I might sing a lot of different songs.
結構、いろいろ歌うかも
That's right.
そうなんだ
Yeah.
うん
Oh my gosh.
やばー
I'd like to hear your voice, but I'm still feeling a bit...
ちょっと声聞きたいけど、やっぱりなんかちょっと、
I'm next door
隣にいる
and.
と
Eh.
えー
It's starting to get worse.
から くなってきた
Well, it might be a bit embarrassing.
えー、恥ずかしいかも、ちょっと
It's okay.
大丈夫よ
I can't see it.
見えない
Eh, no.
えー、やだ
Eh.
えー
Cold.
冷て
Until it cools down.
冷めるまで
Ah, but this is a cami.
あ、でもこれ、キャミだから
Ah, it's cold.
あー、冷めました
Somehow,
なんか、
I just couldn't stand it at all.
ちょっと、 全然なんか我慢できなかった
Your skin is really beautiful.
ほんと、肌きれいだよね
If you look at it in bright light, it's true.
明るいところで見ると、ほんとさ、
The beauty of your skin really stands out.
なんか肌のきれいさ、際立つよ
real?
ほんと?
Yeah.
うん
Eh, why is that?
えー、なんでそれ?
picture?
え?
Eh, do you like that kind of thing?
えー、そういうの好きなの?
yeah?
ん?
I want to be unable to move for a while.
ちょっと動けなくしたい
Eh, okay.
えー、いいよ
ankles,
足首とさ、
Thin legs.
細 い足
Well, you're really good at putting it on.
てか、めっちゃ器用につけるんだよ
In fact, there's something I'm not good at, that.
むしろなんか俺苦手だろ、それ
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
Yeah.
うん
You didn't even cry for a while.
一時帯も泣くのしてんじゃん
It's getting hard.
硬くなってる
It's wet here too.
こっちも濡れてんじゃん
It's so curvy, it's so cute.
めっちゃくねくねしてるの、超かわいい
Balance the volume of the waist, neck and buttocks,
ウエストの首でとお尻のボリュームのバランス、
That's terrible.
やばいね
Please take care of me.
お世話してください
She's cute no matter how she looks.
どんな格好しててもかわいい
That suits you, really.
それ似合うじゃん、めっちゃ